{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4469","name":"MGM-Wolfgang Puck Pizzeria & Cucina","address":"1777 Third St","zipcode":"48226","owner":"MGM Grand Detroit Casino","licenseNumber":"060148","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Permanently Closed","riskCategory":"Low","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.06068,42.33472","geojson":{"id":"4469","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.0606819449999,42.334723771]},"properties":{"name":"MGM-Wolfgang Puck Pizzeria & Cucina","owner":"MGM Grand Detroit Casino","address":"1777 Third St","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Low","license_number":"060148","establishmentid":"4469","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Permanently Closed","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/2/2017"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3617","name":"DTE Energy Town Square C-Store313","address":"2000 Second Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"429","name":"PJ's Lager House","address":"1254 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3598","name":"Cass Technical High School","address":"2501 Second Ave","zipcode":"48201-34"},{"establishmentid":"2675","name":"Brooklyn Street Local","address":"1266 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1405","name":"Mariner's Inn","address":"445 Ledyard","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3966","name":"Bookies Bar and Grille","address":"2208 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"545","name":"Nemos","address":"1378 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4916","name":"Republic Tavern","address":"1942 Grand River","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1349","name":"Mudgie's","address":"1300 Porter St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4648","name":"Ottava Via","address":"1400 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"918","name":"Most Holy Trinity School","address":"1229 LaBrosse St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5416","name":"Lady of the House, LLC","address":"1426 Bagley Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4655","name":"Leland House","address":"400 Bagley Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"720","name":"Lucy & Ethel's Diner","address":"400 Bagley Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3173","name":"Harry's Detroit","address":"2482 Clifford","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","address":"1950 Trumbull","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"500","name":"McShane's","address":"1460 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4939","name":"Batch Brewing Company","address":"1408 Porter St","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4938","name":"UFO Factory","address":"2110 Trumbull St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1140","name":"Masonic Temple","address":"500 Temple","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"45172","inspectionDate":"2018-09-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (beverage)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (prep)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Espresso machine","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\r\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\r\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\r\n         (2)     The container; and\r\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Beverage container","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored improperly","subProblem":"With clean equipment/utensils/linens","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"3-304.13","violationDescription":"LINENS and napkins may not be used in contact with FOOD unless they are used to line a container for the service of FOODS and the LINENS and napkins are replaced each time the container is refilled for a new CONSUMER.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Linen(s) and napkin(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In contact with food(s)","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (prep)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."}]},{"inspectionid":"39691","inspectionDate":"2017-08-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"DISHWASHING ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"Under and around the Counter(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"DISHWASHING ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"38119","inspectionDate":"2017-02-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Equipment/utensils","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Allows for contamination","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In front of","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4469"}}